THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
Isn't the ice cream so sweet?
It's my favorite.
Yeah, even the ice cream's sweet.
I still can't believe it.
I like you, and you like me back.
What are the chances, really?
I know, right? It's so cool.
I'll...
remember this day for a long time.
If we ever get disappointed in
or mad at each other
let's remind ourselves of today.
Let's think about the astronomical odds
we beat to get here and get through it.
Okay.
But I'll be so good to you
that you won't even have to think that.
Do you want to walk more
until we finish this?
Sounds good.
You should go home now.
We're going to stay out all night
at this rate.
It already feels
like it's getting brighter.
You think so?
Everything goes by so quickly
when I'm with you.
So, what are you doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Nothing much.
I usually do nothing
and recharge on Sundays.
Do you want to do nothing with me
tomorrow at my house?
At your house?
Yeah.
Sure, I'll come to your place
around lunch tomorrow.
Maybe 1 p.m.?
Come at noon. I'll cook for you.
I can't wait!
Don't set your expectations too high.
Bye, then.
See you tomorrow. No.
See you real soon.
I can't believe it.
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
EPISODE 9
That night
I couldn't stop thinking
about how cruel love can be.
Could you give this to her for me?
She lives here. Her name is Lee Ui-yeong.
I remember you from last time.
Why don't you give it to her yourself?
Please help me.
Oh, sure.
Love makes us burn with passion
only to lead us to a dead end.
It teaches us
the joy of being with someone else
only to have every little thing
make us anxious
that it won't last.
I really wanted to do well this time.
TIME'S UP
Maybe that's why
it felt so miraculous
that we felt the same way
at the same time.
Love will always be cruel
but I know I'm stronger.
I'll be good to her.
It's better to stick to a recipe
I know will work.
Oh, it's Tae-seop!
Huh?
- Hi, Mother.
- Hey, Tae-seop!
I'm trying to make tteokbokki at home.
What's your recipe for the sauce?
Tteokbokki?
Oh, is Sua coming over?
You want the milder version, then?
No, the spicy version for adults.
For adults...
Oh! Are you...
cooking for that lady?
Yeah.
We're dating now.
They're dating now!
Okay, let me give you the spiciest recipe!
You know how I made your dad fall for me
with my cooking!
I knew I couldn't promise you
a queen's life without chores
after I had your food.
Well, I hope it works for me, too.
Of course!
Start taking notes.
Gochujang, chili powder, sugar, and MSG.
Don't forget minced garlic and scallions.
Oh, and canola oil!
Canola oil?
Oh, yeah, that's the secret
of every tteokbokki master.
That brings all the flavors together.
How much do I add of each thing?
Yeah, anything's possible.
I need matching lingerie.
What would be the best?
Mom!
Mom! Have you seen my light blue blouse?
Yeah, that!
Oh, gosh! What was that about? My hair!
Make me some ramyeon. With an egg.
- Now?
- Yeah.
I'm heading out for lunch.
I'll heat the water for you.
Next time, okay? Sorry, and thanks.
She looks like a kid
who's about to go on a field trip.
Is she seeing someone?
- Excuse me!
- Hello.
Yeah, that's you.
The tall young guy left this with me
last night.
It's yours, right?
Oh, yeah, it is. Thank you.
Make sure to let him know you got it.
Okay.
Hey, Ji-su.
Thanks for returning the cardigan to me.
Did you get home safely last night?
Thanks for the cardigan.
- Ta-da. Congratulations
- Hm?
you finally have a girlfriend.
Thanks, I'll take good care of them.
It smells amazing.
I can't wait!
Some scallions and eomuk.
That's how you make your tteokbokki.
Every household has a different style.
How does your family cook it?
My family?
Our style is not having a style.
Hmm?
My mom was always so busy,
we just bought it from different shops.
So, we don't have a go-to recipe
for kimchi jjigae, either.
I see.
Oh! Can you add all the eomuk?
You want more?
- You like eomuk.
- This looks amazing!
Here.
- Try some.
- Okay.
I'll start with the tteok.
How is it?
- It's amazing!
- Is it?
I'm so glad.
I'll try the eomuk now.
Gosh, you were so pale
and so tiny!
How did such a tiny person grow so big?
I hit a growth spurt in 11th grade.
I see.
I see your parents!
How come you don't have any photos
from when you were in school?
Oh, that was when my father's company
went bankrupt
and he opened the restaurant with Mom.
I see.
Was that the time
you didn't have a dining table at home?
Yeah.
Here.
My dad's really clever.
It was a stressful time for everyone
so he thought it'd be a great idea
to sell spicy chicken feet
in an area
full of stressed office workers.
He entirely relied on my mom's cooking.
I see.
It must've been tough to sell chicken feet
at their very first restaurant.
Whenever they got tired
they leaned on each other to stay strong.
I see
why you think
getting married is so natural.
- This is my first time telling you this.
- Yeah?
My parents separated years ago.
I see.
It's their personalities.
They're too different.
Maybe that's why
but thinking about getting married seems
like none of my business.
And it also makes dating harder for me.
It's like tteokbokki and kimchi jjigae.
I don't know what to look for.
But that's okay.
Do what you did earlier.
You can add extra eomuk
and whatever you like.
Let's build a relationship
the way we want.
Sounds good.
Oh, then...
- Since we're dating now...
- Yeah?
This.
Can you give this to me?
I don't know. I don't have many photos
where I look that cute.
What?
All of these photos are so cute!
Okay, bring a cute baby photo of you
next time.
Let's exchange them.
- Does it have to be just as cute?
- Of course.
Not sure if I have any.
It won't be easy to find one.
Oh?
- Just a sec.
- Okay.
Hello? Hey, I'm...
Ui-yeong!
What? Are you crying?
Can you come over to my place right now?
Right now?
She meant it...
She did not...
Of course, she meant it!
She got her fingers dirty
to rip the skin off for me...
Man, you're an idiot!
You're so stupid!
You're such a chicken!
Seung-jun!
Yeah, that's me...
How much did you drink?
Who are you?
Oh, he's my boyfriend.
I was with him when you called.
- Say hi.
- Hello, I'm Song Tae-seop.
- Your boyfriend?
I see...
Hello, I'm Lim Seung-jun.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
My Ui-yeong finally has a boyfriend!
Even she has a boyfriend...
What about me?
What are you doing? We're in public!
Let's head out. Come on.
I'll take him.
Please get up.
Watch your step.
I'm sorry!
- Gosh.
- Be careful.
Oh, goodness.
That moron!
You okay?
How much did you drink?
- You're ridiculous.
- Lie down first.
Oh.
- Seriously.
- Take this.
You're so nice for someone I just met.
You know
she needs a lot more care
than most people.
She's a handful and then some.
Yeah? That's cute.
You know, you've been a handful, too.
Sorry.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Why would you go this far?
You were too busy talking about yourself.
Were you even curious
about how I've been doing?
We can't just assume
people on dating apps are less serious
than those on blind dates.
I can testify to that.
You know how many weirdos go
on blind dates?
You want me to remind you
of all my bad dates?
So, how many blind dates have you been on?
Just a few.
Just tell her you were too close-minded
and apologize for saying
those on apps aren't serious.
And explain that you were just scared!
No, I can't.
Why not?
She blocked me.
She blocked you?
She didn't have to go that far.
Hey, forget it.
You can't date someone like that.
She'd always make you anxious
if you dated her.
Just get over her.
Get over her, okay?
You will, right?
Answer me!
Seriously.
Stop crying.
Gosh, Seung-jun.
Seung-jun played basketball
back in the day.
- But he had to quit after a major injury.
- I see.
So, it took a lot of hard work
to open that gym.
He may seem strong on the outside
but I know his heart is so fragile.
So, I just always wish
he'd take the easy way.
But you'll be there for him
whenever he needs your help.
Of course, that's my job.
Sorry for dragging you
into this mess today.
No, we ate tteokbokki and met your friend.
It feels like we've gotten closer,
so I'm happy.
I feel the same.
Staying home was even better
than a staycation at a hotel.
Do you like hotel staycations?
Yeah, it's also a good chance
to learn about other hotels.
- I see.
- Do you want to go sometime...
Let's go together sometime.
Whenever you want.
Sounds good.
How's work these days? Are you busy?
I'll be busy for a while
because of the exhibition.
I see.
When can we meet next...
- Saturday.
- Saturday?
That way, we can hang out late.
Oh, that's true.
This is great.
Have a good day.
Happy Monday!
HAVE A GOOD DAY. HAPPY MONDAY!
Why do we have to change the gift set
that has no problems?
They really don't care
about all the time we have to spend
to visit the producers!
Do you think there was an issue
with the quality?
Not at all! We have such high standards!
Whatever, Mr. Oh will take care of it.
He hates extra work more than anyone.
Why are you so tired?
We haven't even had the meeting.
Sorry?
I have a lot going on in my life.
What happened? Oh!
You want some?
Oh?
Didn't I get this for you last time?
Yeah, this kept me going
until the end of the day.
- Take one and feel better.
-You're the best.
What is it? Give me one.
Here, have one.
I'm already so exhausted.
- Let's go!
- Okay, let's go.
Right on.
Our gift set isn't competitive
in the market
especially with online markets offering
high-quality produce.
That's why we want to make a new gift set.
It feels like food trends come and go
even more quickly now.
Even trending tteokbokki and pasta recipes
on social media platforms
- change so often.
- Yeah.
But do we really need to keep up
with every trend?
We're a hotel, after all.
- Don't you agree?
- Hmm?
Oh, sure.
Yeah, we can't follow every trend.
But shouldn't we change something
if the sales are dropping?
Can't Marketing change its approach
to increase the sales?
I've done some thinking
and have you heard of the project,
"Ark of Taste"?
- "Ark"?
- "Ark of Taste"?
No, I've never heard of it.
It's a project aimed to preserve
food varieties.
Its list includes a few Korean items, too.
You came so prepared.
Let's see.
It fits the values the hotel promotes
and it should also interest people
looking to spend their money meaningfully.
This is going to be really hard.
We'll have to travel all over the country!
I guess we'll really prove ourselves
if we pull off such a complicated project.
Right?
CONFERENCE ROOM
The Senior Managing Director is
really looking forward to it.
As you know, he likes to buy a bunch
for his friends and family.
This is a good chance for us.
Let's do well and impress Management.
- Let's do that.
- Got it.
Alright.
How are you going to find producers?
I'll make a list of products we can get
from our current suppliers first.
I'll call the suppliers, then.
And we'll need to travel
to find new suppliers for the others.
We can go to the market together.
Sure.
Good luck, everyone.
- Okay.
- Good work.
HAVE A GOOD DAY. HAPPY MONDAY!
Are you that happy?
Not even Sua thinks so much
about what each emoji means.
Why not? It's great. She sent me a heart.
Stars can be interpreted in so many ways
but not a heart. That's just love.
Enjoy it while you can.
I'm so happy as your friend
that you're dating her now
but as your co-CEO,
I'll have to ask you to select the pieces
for the exhibition
before I throw your phone away.
I was getting on that, okay?
EXHIBITION PROPOSAL
FOR FINDING DAILY HARMONY
PURPOSE OF THE EXHIBITION
THE EXHIBITION STRIVES TO CONNECT
DESIGNERS' PHILOSOPHIES TO LIVING OBJECTS
OUR LIVES ARE FILLED WITH HARMONIES
OF DIFFERENT RHYTHMS AND SENSES
What's so hard about this?
Everything's up to you.
That's why it's harder.
Because there's no set client.
Watch your step.
- We're turning a corner.
- Yes.
Go straight.
This way.
- What are they doing?
- No idea.
Okay.
Put your hand down, and open your eyes.
- Ta-da!
Wait! Is this my chair?
Really?
Yeah, you can even write your name.
We'll send it to your home.
A comfortable seat
you can stay in for hours
and a backrest that supports
your back perfectly!
Give it a try. Chairs feel different
when you sit on them.
It's so cushy!
I love it so much!
This is the best present I've ever gotten.
- Really?
The gift givers seem even happier
than the recipient.
That's how gifts work.
No, you wouldn't know that.
You only ever make things for your clients
and give your parents
the ones with flaws or mistakes.
You've never made anything
for anyone as a gift, have you?
Yeah, I've never done that.
I've never felt that feeling.
This is a perfect chance
to get me a gift, then.
No.
No, right?
No. Hey, you like the chair?
THESE DESIGNS WILL BE MORE THAN OBJECTS.
THEY WILL SPARK EMPATHY AND INTERACTIONS
I'm glad you got your idea.
So, what are you building?
I'll tell you later.
I think I'll have a chance
to show it to you.
- Are you heading home after dinner?
- Yeah.
Hyun-min's been feeling down all day,
and I'm worried.
I want to get her some good food.
Don't forget your dinner.
Okay, enjoy your dinner.
Okay.
A SEAT FOR LOVERS
THAT FEELS WARM AND AFFECTIONATE
SOMETHING THAT WILL MOLD TO THE BODY
OVER TIME...
HONEST AND COMFORTABLE
Hey, sorry.
Order whatever you want. It's on me.
- Really?
- Yeah!
- I'm getting drinks, then.
- Sure.
Excuse me! A bottle of Baijiu, please!
Okay.
Why were you in the bathroom for so long?
Is something wrong?
No, I was just on the phone
with Tae-seop.
What's there to talk about
when the project's over?
Well...
Oh!
I'm dating him now.
Since the farewell party.
No way! Did you two meet that night?
Yeah, I was so late
that I wasn't sure if he'd still be there
but there he was, dozing off
while waiting for me.
Isn't that so funny?
Sure.
As long as he makes you laugh,
that's great.
Congratulations, Ui-yeong!
Thanks.
I can't believe
all those blind dates are finally over.
I know!
Congratulations!
Our drink is here.
Thank you.
This calls for a celebration shot.
Sure.
Thank you.
Gosh, I'm stuffed.
So, how do you
- do it?
- What?
Build a close relationship based on trust?
Trust?
Trust just comes naturally
when you spend time together.
They say it's different dating someone
and marrying someone.
It seems like guys date certain women,
then marry other women.
That's just what they all say.
How can you predetermine
where your relationship is going
before dating someone?
But guys do that.
What? Did someone say something to you?
Who was it?
I recently met a guy on an app.
- That dating app?
- No!
It wasn't a dating app!
Soonmu Market.
Soonmu?
Oh.
I guess a lot of people
meet people on it nowadays.
Excuse me!
We'll get one more bottle Baijiu!
- Okay.
- Hurry.
Are you okay?
- Are you done?
- Yeah.
Is it really bad?
I shouldn't have let you drink so much.
Get in bed first.
Seriously.
Hyun-min, I've known you long enough.
I know you're different
but you're not the type to betray anyone.
If a man can't see that, just let him go.
You got that?
He's already gone.
- I'm taking a day off tomorrow.
- Okay.
Feel better.
I'll leave some water and a hangover cure.
Take it, okay?
Alright...
Gosh, she's been drinking so much.
You're so stupid! You're such a chicken!
It seems like guys date certain women,
then marry other women.
I got the series second-hand
over the weekend.
You know the girl I sold my comics to?
Hey, forget it.
You can't date someone like that.
She'd always make you anxious
if you dated her.
I recently met a guy on an app.
Soonmu Market.
You know the girl I sold my comics to?
DEUKGEUN DEUKGEUN GYM
I'm home.
Hey.
Mom.
Why is the world so small?
- Why?
- I think my friend and my coworker...
have a thing going on.
Who? Seung-jun?
Did you set them up?
No.
I think I actually might've gotten
in their way.
What?
I know you're close to them,
but you're not in this relationship.
Don't get involved, okay?
Maybe they didn't tell you
because they weren't serious.
Yeah, this is between them.
It's not like I can fix anything
by getting involved.
We got the other items sorted
so we just need to find tiger cattle beef.
Alright, let's go.
One person at this big market has to know
a local tiger cattle farmer.
- First...
- Let's see.
Should we start from here?
Okay.
- Hello.
- Do you sell tiger cattle beef?
- No.
- Do you know anyone who does?
- Not at this market.
MEAT FROM FEMALE KOREAN COWS
- Hello!
- Hello.
Do you sell tiger cattle beef here?
No, we don't.
- Really?
- No.
- Thank you, have a good day.
- Bye.
LIST OF BUTCHERS
- Hello, sir.
- Hi.
Do you know a tiger cattle farmer?
- No, I don't.
- No?
Thank you.
That's a no.
We don't sell it.
Okay, thank you. Have a good day.
- Did you find any?
- No.
Let's check the rest.
- I'll go this way, then.
- I'll text you.
We don't sell it.
Okay, thank you.
LIST OF BUTCHERS
We've checked almost every shop.
I know. Why is it so hard to find?
It says there's a butcher shop here.
Really? I thought I just saw an herb shop.
Let me go to Mr. Shin's shop
before it closes, then.
- Call me if you find anything.
- Okay.
OREUM BUTCHER SHOP
Hello, sir.
I'm from The Hills Hotel.
- You want anything?
- No, not now.
I just wanted to ask
if you know of a tiger cattle farm.
Tiger cattle? Let's see.
I can't remember if Mr. Choi raises
tiger cattle or black cows.
Do you know someone? Where is his farm?
It's somewhere in Gangwon-do
or Gyeongsango-do.
I suddenly can't remember it.
Maybe it's because I haven't made
a lot of sales today.
Oh, gosh, silly me.
I want to get some Korean beef to grill.
I'll take three pounds
of the best part.
Maybe that'll help you remember.
I'm not sure if I'll remember.
Here's three pounds of sirloin
and his number.
Thank you so much! You saved my life.
No, it's nothing.
By the way, Mr. Choi can be a real Grinch.
I'm not sure
if he'll get along with you two.
What's wrong?
Are you worried about what he said?
Yeah, we have a lot to discuss.
His personality matters.
That's true, but you can't raise
a rare breed if you're easygoing.
He has the upper hand in this deal,
so we'll just have to go along with him.
I know, but...
Don't worry about it.
I'll arrange the meeting
and be in charge of all communications.
Okay.
By the way,
you look really happy these days.
- Do I?
- Yeah.
I don't know
why I feel so motivated at my job lately.
But we have to head back and wrap it up.
Let's get some coffee and head back.
- Oh, I...
- Come on!
It's on me.
- "This is..."
- We need some coffee.
Choose what you want.
- Hey.
- Here you go.
- Okay.
- Wait.
I have to take this call.
I'll get an iced Americano.
- Hello.
- Hey
I'll get two iced Americanos to go.
Okay.
Here.
Thanks.
How have you been?
Did you go home safely that day?
Yeah, that was days ago.
How do you think I've been?
Oh, sorry.
No need to be sorry.
You just followed your heart.
I've been busy lately.
I had no time to be sad.
So, did you land a role
after that audition?
Yeah, I think so.
That's so great.
And you? Are you dating Tae-seop now?
Yeah, we're dating now.
- That's why you haven't been here?
- Hmm?
Did he tell you not to come here
or are you giving me space to get closure?
Nothing has to change.
We're just back to being friends.
It's not like we broke up after dating.
Don't be so old-fashioned.
Times have changed.
I promise not to cross the line.
I won't bother you.
All good now?
Okay, then.
Yeah.
Is the coffee ready?
- See you around.
- Bye.
So, we've decided to give you the role,
Ji-su.
Mr. Shin?
Oh, thank you for the opportunity.
Oh, hello.
I didn't know Ji-su was here.
Is this a surprise?
I don't like surprises.
Oh, I caught you off-guard. Sorry.
Have a seat.
I guess you don't talk about acting
with your mother at all.
Why not?
Right.
What's so surprising?
Do you talk about directing
with your mother?
I see what you mean
now that you've put it that way.
I've built my acting career by myself
and I plan on continuing to do so.
We're not related by blood
but he's just like me, straightforward.
Don't tell me you hired Ji-su
because I'm reviewing your next project.
Not at all.
He fit the role best.
I shouldn't have been invited, then.
People will get the wrong idea.
And it's Ji-su's first drama.
I'm sure he'd rather talk to you
in private.
He really doesn't understand actors.
I guess so.
Let me know anytime
you want to talk to me.
Okay, thank you.
I was going to pay for dinner.
I hope you enjoy my script.
I'll enjoy it if it's good.
Your car's waiting. You should go.
I need to talk to Ji-su.
Okay, goodnight.
See you on the set, Ji-su.
I'll do my best
to prevent these meetings from happening
but we can't avoid them completely
if we're in the same field.
I'm aware of that.
Take advantage of it next time.
I'm glad you could keep calm.
You did the same. You stayed calm.
It's nothing.
Congratulations on your new role.
I'll see how you do on TV.
Bye.
Did you get some rest?
Yeah, I feel a lot better now.
I can't let a man make me have regrets.
I've even put the comics back on sale
on Soonmu Market.
I guess you're really over him.
It's not like I didn't try.
I had to block him
in fear that I'd drunk-call him.
So, you blocked him
because you were worried you'd call him?
I also didn't want to get my hopes up
and have him not call me.
It was for both reasons.
No, mind your own business.
You're not a part of this situation.
Leave it to the two.
DEUKGEUN DEUKGEUN GYM
Seung-jun!
What?
Tell me. Hyun...
No, the Soonmu Market girl.
Do you still like her?
Why are you suddenly asking me that?
Just tell me! Do you like her or not?
I do! How can I stop liking her
just overnight?
You know I'm not that cool.
I'm glad.
Come with me.
Is this her?
Yeah, it is. Our memories!
She's really ready to move on!
Pull yourself together!
Why do you think she's selling them?
Because she's trying to get over you!
Get some money ready.
I'll buy them.
I'll buy the comics and everything else
you're selling.
Can we meet somewhere?
How did you know it was her?
Huh? Well, I...
I'll tell you once things work out, okay?
She must've gotten home hours ago.
UI-YEONG
Oh!
Where are you?
Why didn't you read my messages?
I met Seung-jun after work.
Oh, Seung-jun?
Then...
- what about me?
- What?
Didn't you miss me?
I missed you.
Say that again.
What a nice thing to hear.
I miss you, Ui-yeong.
Come and see me.
Did all your employees go home?
Yeah.
So, this is what your office looks like.
It's stunning.
This is where we work on documents
design things, and have meetings.
Over here. This is my desk.
I see. That's the best spot.
It seems like such a chill office.
We have to air it out often
because we have a lot of sawdust.
- I see.
- And this is the woodworking workshop.
The workshop?
You might get splinters,
as it's not processed.
I see.
It's too dangerous. Here.
There are so many interesting tools.
This is the table saw for cutting blocks.
Table saw?
And this is a band saw.
A band saw.
And this is a drilling machine
for drilling holes.
A drilling machine.
I can't remember that. It's too hard.
Oh, can you help me with something
since you're already here?
What is it?
I need measurements for a sample chair
to submit for the exhibition.
I feel like I'm giving too many details
about me.
No, I still have a long way to go.
I want to know you more.
I don't think we should just meet
on weekends. I'm too busy.
Let's just meet whenever we want.
That sounds like a plan.
Mr. Song!
Mr. Song? Did he go home?
Man, we got you snacks.
That leaves us with no choice.
We'll need some beer if he's not here.
Jin-su, get some from the store!
Okay, you like beer, right?
Are we allowed to drink?
Of course not.
Mr. Song lets us do anything here
but drink or date.
Those are non-negotiables.
Why? Because it's too thrilling
that you get hot.
It's dangerous.
- Cheers!
It's extra good today.
This is the best!
- Let's dig in.
- Dig in!
My legs hurt.
- Your legs?
- Yeah, hold on.
What was that?
Who's there?
- That's scary.
- Who's there?
Bo-yoon...
Where are you going? Sae-byeok?
Darn it.
Huh?
- Jin-su.
- Yeah?
Go.
Darn it!
Come out!
I'm calling the cops!
We have weapons!
You'd better come out in three.
One.
Two.
Three!
Hey, guys.
What are you doing there?
- Huh?
- Gosh, my legs.
Oh, hi.
Huh? Ui-yeong!
Hi, Sae-byeok.
It's great seeing you fitting in so well
at your new job.
What are you two doing here?
We...
We're dating.
Ui-yeong and Mr. Song?
You said no dating in office!
That's too dangerous!
You guys are drinking here, too!
That's also dangerous.
Huh?
Congratulations.
Ms. Big Discounts?
Mr. Choco Killer?
Choco...
I knew it.
You don't even eat chocolate!
How are you "Choco Killer"?
Using someone else's account
can get you banned from the app for life.
You know that?
No, I don't. Report me if you want.
Soonmu Market just reminds me of you,
anyway.
I'll delete my account and delete the app.
After this deal.
It's 50,000 won. The deal's done.
Give me the money.
Not just like this.
Make another bet with me.
If you beat me, you get 100,000 won.
No, I'll give you 150,000 won.
You think we're at a market? Forget it.
How much more do I need to pay
for you to take it?
What if you win?
I know you're trying to get something
out of this.
Just...
hear me out.
That's all I need.
I was too embarrassed to say this
but I was on the basketball team.
I was training to go pro until college
but had to quit after a crucifix injury.
That was when I started being so careful,
mentally and physically.
That was why I easily assumed things
about you.
I was afraid I'd get hurt,
so I hurt you first.
I'm sorry.
I'm only supposed to hear you out
if you win.
Tell me after you win.
I can't hear you!
Come on. Go.
TIME'S UP
The moment you give up, the game's over.
I really like you.
I really wanted to tell you this.
Was the trip here okay?
- It was okay.
- Here.
Hello.
- He's here.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you.
IDAE FARM'S SPECIAL STRATEGY
WITH THE SPECIAL TIGER CATTLES
This is amazing.
I know!
My tiger cattles are bred
with the healthiest cows
from all over the country
directly at the farm.
I raise each one with love,
like it's my own child.
We'll make sure to treat
your precious tiger cattles well.
As you should!
You know, miss
your beautiful, sparkly eyes
look just like my tiger cattles' eyes!
Your tiger cattles?
I see the resemblance.
That's a first for me. Thank you.
I'm really thirsty.
Is there anything to drink?
Something sweet.
I'll get some juice, then.
We'll get some cookies, too.
- We'll be right back.
- I feel bad now.
We should've prepared some in advance.
We're sorry.
He's not grumpy at all.
I know!
I'm so glad.
- Hey
- Yes?
I'm looking for a long-term partner
whom I can trust.
We're looking for the same.
We can start with this project
and build a long-term partnership.
- By the way
- Yes?
you know the lady with the bright eyes?
Bright eyes?
Oh, yes.
Does she have a boyfriend?
Why are you asking that?
My youngest son is single
because he only ever cares
about our tiger cattles.
He hasn't dated anyone in forever.
It'd be nice to get
the youngsters to talk business
and maybe bond over talks about life.
There's no partnership
stronger and more solid than that!
Oh, I see.
That's what you mean by a partnership.
Okay.
Damn it.
Things went so smoothly.
I'll take care of discussing the details
and signing the contract...
No, that's okay.
Let's have Ui-yeong do it.
- Sorry?
- Hmm?
But Na-ri found the farm
arranged the meeting,
and did the research.
I know
but just do it, okay?
We need to work on the recipes, too
and I know Chef Park trusts you.
- But...
- And Na-ri
- good work.
- Mr. Oh!
Why am I always tired these days?
Maybe I have a bad liver.
So, I'll have to meet them
tomorrow after work.
But Na-ri won't hand over anything.
She must be really disappointed.
It won't be easy to start from scratch
and be ready in a day.
But I feel better after telling you this.
Even though nothing's sorted.
You can tell me anything anytime.
Oh, why don't I pick you up
after work tomorrow?
No, I don't even know when I'll be done.
Let's just meet on the weekend.
Are you working until late today?
Yeah, but it's not so bad
now that I've delegated the work.
I'll call you again when I get home.
Okay.
HANKUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
DIRECTOR INAUGURATION CEREMONY
Hello.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
- It's an honor to meet you.
- I'm flattered. Thank you.
It's so exciting
to be able to introduce you as my wife
to everyone.
I'm not good at being a wife.
I'm just here to congratulate you, too.
I know.
- That was why I invited you.
- Hmm?
I saw how good you were at applauding
at that awards ceremony.
Next, we'll award Dr. Shin
with an appreciation plaque
and hear his inauguration speech
as the new Director.
Dear distinguished colleagues
I will bear my position as the Director
of HKUH with great weight.
Moreover, I'll sacrifice myself
to make HKUK a leader of medicine.
All of you have made great contribution
to build
the hospital's reputation and value.
I'll do my best as the Director
to keep up the reputation and value.
Thank you.
One, two, three.
One more.
- Thank you.
You're even more beautiful in person!
Hello.
I hear you were his patient,
and that was how you met.
And you traveled to Cannes together.
It was a coincidence.
We're doctors, too.
How come we don't meet celebrities?
He's just another doctor, like you.
Did you two get close in Cannes?
Well, you know...
See you around.
Please help Dr. Shin
with his new position.
Thank you.
So, they didn't meet at the hospital,
but it was still an affair.
It's even worse, consdering how his wife
was almost dying.
Who doesn't know about him
ignoring calls from the hospital
and his son when he went to France?
I know, right?
How can someone be so cruel?
You really can't trust anyone, huh?
Hello.
Ui-yeong!
- Oh, hello.
- Hi.
You look great today.
Really? Thanks.
I know you've gone
on a lot of blind dates lately.
- Yeah.
- But as you know
blind dates are good experience,
even if things don't work out.
And sometimes, you get lucky
and find a good one.
- I guess so.
- Yeah.
I booked a table at Harrod in Cheongdam.
Take the card.
Order whatever you want with it, okay?
So, Mr. Choi's youngest son is coming?
And he butchers tiger cattles?
He should be around your age,
considering Mr. Choi's age.
He basically runs a moo-d-sized company
with all those expensive cows
running around in that big farm.
So funny.
- Anyway, good luck.
- Sure.
Moo-d-sized...
Na-ri.
Here.
What is it?
All the docs for today's meeting.
I'll do my best not to ruin
all the hard work you put in
and make sure the meeting goes well.
Okay.
Mr. Oh, can I see you at the cafe
by the hotel after work?
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
What did you want to talk about?
I'm so mad.
- Hmm?
- I know Ui-yeong is good.
She motivates me, too.
But you went too far with this project!
You know I worked late nights
for days for this!
I know. I really do. Who doesn't?
I know you worked hard on it.
Why did you do this, then?
I know I can do well.
I can go to the meeting right now...
Hey! Stop it.
A no is a no! Don't be like that.
Stay still if you don't want to ruin it,
okay?
Why? At least tell me why!
You have...
a family!
Whatever! I'm going home.
- Whatever.
- Myeong-un!
The more I think about it,
the worse it gets.
Sure, I've skipped a few site visits
by using my family and in-laws
as an excuse.
But I've worked here for long enough
to do that.
How can he throw me out of a project
just for that?
Because I have a family?
How does that make any sense?
It's so odd for him to stop you
from trying to work harder.
When's the meeting?
I'm sure she's on her way now.
They're meeting at Harrod
in Cheongdam or something.
People have work meetings at such places?
Why? Do you know the place?
Yeah, I used to work there.
It's not really a business meeting vibe.
It's a famous spot in the area
for blind dates.
Hold up.
Mr. Choi's son is coming to the meeting.
I can't go as a married woman... No way.
- A blind date?
Are you Ms. Lee Ui-yeong?
Are you Mr. Choi's youngest son?
- Yeah.
- Hello.
I'm Lee Ui-yeong from Purchasing
at The Hills Hotel.
Oh, a business card.
- I'm Choi U-jun.
- I see.
The traffic on the way was terrible!
It was a long drive, right?
It's fine.
Should we head in?
- Oh, sure.
- Okay.
This is perfect. I was getting hungry.
Would you like to have dinner?
Yeah, a dinner.
Okay.
The menu's hard to read.
Please order some good meat for me.
Oh, sure. Meat.
Excuse me.
We'll take two steaks, please.
Okay, how would you like them cooked?
If it's fresh, medium-rare.
If not, medium.
Oh, and wine! You want wine?
We'll take two.
Okay, we'll get them ready soon.
Thank you.
- What should we do?
- The device you’re trying to reach...
I can't reach Mr. Oh or Ui-yeong.
Hello?
Hey, honey.
Are you off now?
Yeah, I'll be home soon. Bye.
I'd better get going.
I'll keep calling her when I get home.
- She'll pick up eventually.
- Okay.
My gosh.
- Hello.
- Is everything good?
- Actually, something urgent came up.
Can I go home a bit early?
Huh? Oh, sure.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
My father said
your eyes resembled
our cows' eyes at the farm.
He was right.
Everyone fights over those cows
with bright eyes at the market.
Funny how you're still single, huh?
You think so?
Oh, this is the proposal from the hotel.
Oh.
Do I read it now?
ARK OF TASTE SELECTION:
PROPOSAL FOR TIGER CATTLE BEEF SET
That's the first draft.
Idae Farm can decide
on what's in the set and the quantities.
Oh, here comes our food!
Why don't we eat first?
Sure.
Thank you.
This looks great!
Is this raw or something?
I can crush you.
I bet you didn't know
I was a butcher, huh?
I guess it's my time to shine.
Sir...
You have to use this knife.
Oh!
I must look like such a country bumpkin
in your eyes, huh?
Oh, not at all.
I also use scissors to eat meat at home.
You're a lot more chill than you seem!
Well, nice to meet you.
One more glass!
Hey! Don't be stingy.
Fill the glass to the rim, alright?
Okay.
Hey!
Man, I'm getting hot!
If I drink more
we won't be able to talk business
- and I won't even manage to get home.
- Hey...
Why are you so far away?
We, butchers
always end up arm wrestling
in the middle of our shifts!
Our forearms are so strong
that we can't stop ourselves.
Touch it.
What? No, thanks.
It's fine, I'm older! Go ahead.
I can tell by the look of it.
Don't be so shy.
I guess you haven't dated many men.
You're old enough to know everything.
It's not fun
when a woman keeps acting so innocent.
So, how many men have you dated?
Three? Four?
He's the worst of the worst.
Mr. Choi
Yeah?
this is a business meeting.
- Huh?
- Please refrain from asking
unrelated questions.
Why do you keep talking about work
all evening?
Just be good to me, go along with me
and all that business talk will go well!
Isn't that why you've been so nice to me
all evening?
Let's just be honest, okay?
To be honest, the only reason
I'm being cordial is
that I want to convince you
to trust and respect the hotel.
I have no interest
in building a personal relationship.
- Huh?
- So, Mr. Choi
please get back to considering
whether the deal can be profitable to you.
Instead of me.
You can read our proposal.
I need to call my supervisor.
Hold on.
That's condescending of you.
Sit down.
Sit down right now!
You've had too much to drink.
Let's end the meeting here.
I'll call you another time.
Where the hell are you going?
That hurts! Let go!
You think you can just leave?
- Let go! It hurts!
- No!
Tae-seop!
Who the hell are you?
Me? Her boyfriend.
THE PRACTICAL GUIDE TO LOVE
CONGRATULATIONS,
YOU FINALLY HAVE A GIRLFRIEND
I REALLY LIKE YOU
TOO DANGEROUS
How did you know to come here?
Until the Disciplinary Committee decides
what to do with Mr. Oh...
There's nothing to do.
You know things you've been putting off
because you've been busy.
Do those, one by one.
It's for you.
I'm getting a divorce.
What?
You have to get back to work soon
so it'll be nice to go on a trip,
even if it's short.
Dad!
Your father?
Subtitles by: Min-sun Kim